Toni Morrison Papers, 1908-2017: Finding Aid C1491
mss EADs that duplicate ones in Manuscripts
- Working Files, 1955-2018; 68 boxes
  - Office Working Files III, 1960-2013; 19 boxes
    - Accepted Lectures, 1989-2008; 2 boxes
      - SCLC Speech, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 23)
        January 15, 1990.
    - Accepted Louvre, 2004-2007; 1 box
      - Louvre Press, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 24)
      - American Friends of the Louvre, 2005-2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 25)
      - Miscellaneous Artists, Paris, 2005-2007; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 26)
      - Family/Guests, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 27)
      - Dominique Bourgois, 2004-2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 28)
      - Luggage, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 29)
      - Miscellaneous Invites, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 30)
      - Francoise B-D Institute Reading, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 31)
        November 28, 2006.
      - Vienna, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 32)
        November 19-20, 2006.
      - Loyrette Lunch (Cancelled), 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 33)
        November 21, 2006.
      - Penne Festival, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 34)
        November 23-24, 2006.
      - Ancient Lectures, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 35)
      - Interviews, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 36)
      - Lucas Barron, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 37)
      - Museum Lecture, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 38)
        November 15, 2006.
      - Slam Poetry, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 39)
        November 10 and 25, 2006.
      - Jeannie Viadero, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 40)
      - Fritz Party, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 41)
        November 4, 2006.
      - NYPL Library Lions, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 42)
        November 13, 2006.
      - Opening Lecture, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 43)
        November 6, 2006.
      - Forsythe Discussion/Lecture, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 44)
        November 8, 2006.
      - Logistics/Schedule for Louvre, 2005-2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 45)
      - Journee-rencontre avec Toni Morrison, 2006 March 21; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 46)
      - Louvre Speech Research, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 47)
      - The Foreigner's Home Master Log/Transcript, 2006; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 48)
    - Accepted Miscellaneous, 1987-2007; 1 box
      - Slade Postcard, 2007; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 1)
        November 2007.
      - Toni Wofford Morrison School, Lorain, OH, 2007; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 2)
        October 7, 2007.
      - Columbia Open, 2004-2007; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 3)
        September 28, 2007.
      - Family Reunion, 2007; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 4)
        May 17-19, 2007.
      - Shared Interest, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 5)
        March 12, 2007.
      - Forsythe Concert BAM, 2007; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 6)
        March 3, 2007.
      - Cleveland/Progressive, 2006; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 7)
        February 27, 2006.
      - September 21 Appointments, 2005; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - Meeting with Aoi Mori, 2005; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 9)
        April 2005.
      - Clifton Tribute, 2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 10)
        November 18, 2004.
      - Academy of Culture, 2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 11)
        November 9, 2004.
      - Donated Book Cape Cod Library Council, 2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 12)
        August 7-8, 2004.
      - Nina Simone Tribute, 2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 13)
        June 21, 2004.
      - Harlem School of the Arts Fundraiser, 2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 14)
        April 26, 2004.
      - Southern Poverty Law Center Letter, 2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 15)
        April 1, 2004.
      - Africa, 2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 16)
      - Celebrity Charity Chair Auction, 2003; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 17)
        December 3, 2003.
      - Howard Reunion, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 18)
        May 9, 2003.
      - Vanessa Stockton Student Visit, 2003; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 19)
        April 13-15, 2003.
      - University of Cape Town Kofi Annan Honorary Degree, 2002; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 20)
        December 9, 2002.
      - June Jordan Tribute, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 21)
        November 14, 2002.
      - Dialogue: Continuing Leadership, CUNY, 2002; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 22)
        September 20, 2002.
      - June Jordan Memorial, 2002; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 23)
        September 15, 2002.
      - Paris Review Booth Book Expo of America, 2002; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 24)
        May 3, 2002.
      - Cleto Munari Italian Designer, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 25)
      - Visit to Ruth Simmons, 2001; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 26)
        August 4-6, 2001.
      - PSA Award (Sanchez), 2001; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 27)
        April 20, 2001.
      - Children's Home Society of New Jersey, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 28)
        November 2001.
      - Alice Randall Wind Done Gone, 2001; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 29)
        April 15, 2001.
      - Hillary Clinton Inaugural, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 30)
        January 7, 2001.
      - Lawrence Memorial, 2000; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 31)
      - Cosby Foundation Honorary Chair, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 32)
        May 23, 2000.
      - Woman. Life. Song. Premiere, 2000; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 33)
        March 22, 2000.
      - African AIDS Initiative Advisory Board, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 34)
        January 14, 2000.
      - National Book Awards Dinner, 1999; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 35)
        November 17, 1999.
      - Toni Cade Bambara Tribute, 92nd St. Y, 1999; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 36)
        November 15, 1999.
      - National Underground Railroad Freedom Center, 1999-2004; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 37)
        May 1999.
      - Haley Farm Library Dedication, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 38)
        March 19, 1999.
      - Tomb of the Unknown Slave Advisory Board, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 39)
        February 4, 1999.
      - New Yorker Article: March on Washington, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 40)
        January 1999.
      - New York Black 100 Project, 1999; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 41)
      - Peter Joseph Memorial, 1998; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 42)
        November 5, 1998.
      - Leon Forrest Memorial, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 43)
        January 30, 1998.
      - Borders, 1997; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 44)
        November 16, 1997.
      - Prometheus Advisory Board, 1997-2001; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 45)
        May 1, 1997.
      - Jessye Norman Recital, 1997; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 46)
        April 20, 1997.
      - South Africa Book Shipment, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 47)
        December 1996.
      - Guggenheim Musem Frankenthaler Exhibition, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 48)
        October 23, 1996.
      - Toni Morrison Library Neighborhood House, 1996; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 49)
        September 20, 1996.
      - Building Quotation, 1996; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 50)
        August 1996.
      - Guggenheim Museum Honorary Committee, 1996; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 51)
        June 5, 1996.
      - Israeli Consulate, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 52)
        January 16, 1996.
      - Free Library of Philadelphia Auction, 2005; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 53)
        October 20, 1995.
      - McDonald and Company Ad, 1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 54)
        July 26, 1995.
      - Lincoln Center American Visionaries, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 55)
        July 25-26, 1995.
      - Angela Davis Petition, 1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 56)
        July 5, 1995.
      - Tanglewood, 1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 57)
        July 2, 1995.
      - Peace Autograph, 1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 58)
      - Toni Morrison Reading Room Lorain OH Public Library Dedication, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 59)
        January 22, 1995.
      - Ralph Ellison Memorial, 1994; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 60)
        May 26, 1994.
      - Tanglewood, 1993; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 61)
        July 9-10, 1993.
      - Mass of Courage, Arlington VA, 1993; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 62)
        June 6, 1993.
      - Diana Ross, 1993; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 63)
        April 1993.
      - NFAA Fundraiser, 1990-1993; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 64)
        March 6, 1993.
      - FAIR Advisory Board, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 65)
      - Marlon Brando, 1991 February-June; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 66)
      - Everyman's Library Honorary Ed Committee Knopf, 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 67)
      - Women Editorial Board, 1988-1992; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 68)
      - Transition Editorial Board, 1990-2000; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 69)
      - Queens College Advisory Board, 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 70)
      - El Salvador Human Rights Fund Board of Directors, 1990; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 71)
      - Duke Ellington Memorial Fund Board of Directors, 1988-1997; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 72)
      - Human Rights Watch Board, 1989-1994; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 73)
      - Fund for Free Expression Board, 1987; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 74)
    - Accepted Photo Shoots, 1998-2006; 1 box
      - Commissioned Portrait, 2004-2006; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 75)
        February 23, 2005.
      - Vanity Fair Photo Shoot, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 76)
        December 13, 2002.
      - Clemente Ltd. Portrait Sitting, 1998; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 77)
        September 18, 1998.
      - Leibovitz Studio Photo Shoot, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 78)
        September 9, 1998.
    - Accepted Princeton University, 1989-2008; 1 box
      - UCCPA Gala, 2007-2008; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 1)
        November 8-9, 2007.
      - Michael Wood ENG 133, 2007; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 2)
        November 7, 2007.
      - President's Retreat, 2007; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 3)
        April 19, 2007.
      - Toni Morrison Lecture Series, 2006; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 4)
        October 21-22, 2006.
      - Commencement, 2006; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 5)
        June 6, 2006.
      - Party at 280 Nassau, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 6)
      - Friends of the Princeton Library, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 7)
        April 3, 2005.
      - Baccalaureate, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 8)
        May 29, 2004.
      - Cosby Fundraiser, 2003; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 9)
      - Forbes Visit, 1989-2004; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 10)
        February 12, 2004.
      - CW Faculty Reading, 2003; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 11)
        March 2, 2003.
      - Alumni Day Reading, 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 12)
        February 21, 2003.
      - Commencement, 2002; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 13)
        June 4, 2002.
      - Tilghman Installation, 2001; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 14)
        September 28, 2001.
      - Campaign Event, 2000; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 15)
        October 20, 2000.
      - Millenium Lecture, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 16)
        April 18, 2000.
      - Mandela, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 17)
        February 25, 2000.
      - Envisioning Paradise Conference, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 18)
      - Moffett Panel Lecture, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 19)
        April 23, 1998.
      - National Campaign Committee Meeting, 1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 20)
        November 14, 1997.
      - Global Perspectives Symposium, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 21)
        May 9, 1997.
      - Peter Joseph and Michael Kaiser Lunch, 1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 22)
        April 11, 1997.
      - Works in Progress, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 23)
        February 13, 1997.
      - 250th Anniversary, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 24)
        October 25, 1996.
      - Commencement, 1996; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 25)
        June 4, 1996.
    - Accepted Readings, 1989-2007; 2 boxes
      - Astor Memorial NYPL, 2007; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 26)
        September 11, 2007.
      - Tulane University Reading, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 27)
        April 12, 2007.
      - Julia Leigh Reading Intro, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 28)
        December 1, 2005.
      - Guadalajara Book Festival, 2004-2006; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 29)
        November 24-28, 2005.
      - 92nd St Y Reading, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 30)
        November 6, 2005.
      - Gathering of the Tribes Hurricane Benefit, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 31)
        October 1, 2005.
      - New Yorker Benefit, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 32)
        September 24, 2005.
      - Higher Ground Benefit, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 33)
        September 17, 2005.
      - Soyinka Birthday Reading, 2005; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 34)
        April 27, 2005.
      - SummerStage Reading, 2004; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 35)
        August 5, 2004.
      - Hunter College Reading, 2003-2004; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 36)
        May 20, 2004.
      - St. Mary's College, 2002; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 37)
        October 4, 2002.
      - International Festival, Rome/Amalfi, 2002; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 38)
        June 17, 2002.
      - Bill T. Jones, 2002; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 39)
        June 11, 2002.
      - Society of Fellows Reading, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 40)
        March 5, 2002.
      - Styron Intro, 2002; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 41)
        February 13, 2002.
      - Princeton Adult School Reading, 2001-2002; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 42)
        February 12, 2002.
      - Memorial Service, 2001; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 43)
        September 16, 2001.
      - Lannan Foundation, 2001; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 44)
        May 23, 2001.
      - June Jordan Intro (NYU Africana Studies/IAAA), 2000; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 45)
        April 28, 2000.
      - Salisbury, MD Reading, 1999; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 46)
        September 26, 1999.
      - Juneteenth Reading, 1999; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 47)
        July 18, 1999.
      - CW Gala Reading, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 48)
        February 17, 1999.
      - 92nd St Y Reading, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 49)
        February 1, 1999.
      - Philadelphia Reading, 1998; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 50)
        April 8, 1998.
      - National Middle School, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 51)
        October 30, 1997.
      - Butler University, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 52)
        October 29, 1997.
      - St. Louis Public Library, 1996; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 53)
        October 28, 1997.
      - North Suburban Library, 1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 54)
        October 27, 1997.
      - National Black Women's Health Project Reading and Tribute, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 55)
      - Chicago/St. Louis/Indianapolis, 1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 56)
        October 27-31, 1997.
      - Brearly School Reading, 1997; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 57)
      - The Balm in Gilead, 1996; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 58)
        December 4, 1996.
      - Springfield/Smith/CT Colleges, 1996; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 59)
        October 6-7, 1996.
      - Hudson Valley Writers' Center, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 60)
        June 2, 1996.
      - Trustees Meeting, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 61)
        April 12, 1996.
      - NY Philharmonic, 1995; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 62)
        December 14, 1995.
      - Rochester University, 1995; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 63)
        November 6, 1995.
      - Caramoor, 1995; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 64)
        July 30, 1995.
      - Whitney Biennial Reading, 1995; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 65)
        April 25, 1995.
      - City Arts, 1992-1995; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 66)
        April 14, 1995.
      - Mexico UNAM, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 67)
        January 29-February 3, 1995.
      - NYPL Bryant Park Reading, 1994; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 68)
        September 12, 1994.
      - Dreaming Emmett Reading, 1994; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 69)
        July 18, 1994.
      - Twin Elms Reading, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 70)
        September 17, 1993.
      - NYU Reading Seminar, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 71)
        April 2-3, 1993.
      - Race-ing Forum/Reading, 1992; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 72)
        November 17, 1992.
      - Crisis Ministry Reading, 1992; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 73)
        October 18, 1992.
      - African Arts Fund Reading Dawn Zain, 1992; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 74)
        October 15, 1992.
      - Novel of the Americans, Denver, 1992; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 75)
        September 8, 1992.
      - Northwestern Forrest Reading, 1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 1)
        November 9, 1991.
      - Ohio Humanities Council, 1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 2)
        October 31, 1991.
      - Legal Defense Fund (Margaret Goheen), 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 3)
        October 27, 1991.
      - Crisis Ministry Reading, 1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 4)
        October 20, 1991.
      - NYU Humanities Council Reading, 1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 5)
        October 7, 1991.
      - Literarisches Colloquium, Berlin, 1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 6)
        June 1991.
      - CAC Cincinnati, 1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 7)
        April 14, 1991.
      - Washington University, St. Louis Assembly Series Reading, 1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 8)
        March 21, 1991.
      - Union Theological Seminary, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 9)
        March 4, 1991.
    - Accepted Writing, 1993-2007; 1 box
      - Foreward to The Piano Lesson, 2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 10)
      - Church Project Liner Notes, 2003; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 11)
        March 2003. See also Church DVD with audiovisual materials.
      - Jacob Lawrence Memorial, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 12)
      - Ploughshares, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 13)
        Spring 2000.
      - Hank Parnell Congratulatory Letters, 1999; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 14)
        January 12, 1999.
      - "The First Solution" written for L'Observateur, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 15)
        December 10, 1997.
      - CUNY, 1993; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 16)
        June 21, 1993.
    - Declined Awards, 1994-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Declined College and School Appearances, 1996-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Declined Commencements and Honorary Degrees, 2000-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - Declined Conferences, 2004-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Declined Festivals, 2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Declined Fundraisers, 2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 22)
    - Declined Guest Speakers/Keynotes, 2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Declined ICM Jobs, 1995-2006; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Declined Interviews, 1989-2008; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - Declined Invitations, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 26)
    - Declined Lectures, 1989-2003; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 27)
    - Declined Other/Misc., 1998-2004; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 28)
    - Declined Panels and Symposia, 1996-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 29)
    - Declined Readings, 2006-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 30)
    - Declined Receptions, Dinners, Parties, 1994-2003; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 31)
    - Declined Requests for Writing, 1992-2007; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 32)
    - Declined Writer in Residence, 1993-2006; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 33)
    - Academy of Culture, 1992-2005; 6 folders (Box 166, Folder 34-39)
    - Africa Watch, 1989; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 40)
    - African Commentary Magazine, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 41)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1988-2009; 2 folders (Box 166, Folder 42-43)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1988-2002; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 44)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1993-2002; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 45)
    - Amherst College Library, 2007-2008; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Bambara, Toni Cade, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Bambara: Deep Sightings, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Bambara: Foreign Publication/Translator, 1997-2002; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Bambara: Melvin Wilk, Misc. Students, Scholars, 1996-2002; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 22)
      This material is closed until 2026.
    - Bambara: Melvin Wilk Correspondence, 1960-2002; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 23)
    - Bambara: Memorial Transcript, 1995; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Bambara: Those Bones, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - BCCC Advisory Board: Children's Defense Fund, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Bhaba, Homi, 1991-1996; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Biographical Entries, 1985-1998; 1 box
      - African American Writers, 1991; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 9)
      - Authors and Artists, 1988; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 10)
      - Bibliography of American Fiction, 1990; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 11)
      - Black American Women Novelists, 1990; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 12)
      - Black Genius, 1997; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 13)
      - Black Writers, 1993; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 14)
      - Contemporary Authors, 1998; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 15)
      - Dictionary of Literary Biography, 1994; 2 folders (Box 167, Folder 16-17)
      - Wasadizi, 1994; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 18)
      - Modern African American Writers, undated; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 19)
      - The Nobel Laureates of Literature (The Georgia Review ), 1995; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 20)
      - Toni Morrison: An Annotated Bibliography, 1987; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 21)
      - Toni Morrison Bibliography: 1990-1993, 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 22)
      - Bibliography Material, 1985-1997; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 23)
      - Bibliographies, 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 167, Folder 24-25)
    - Bittker, Boris: The Case for Black Reparations, 1971-2002; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 26)
    - Booksign, 2006-2010; 2 folders (Box 167, Folder 27-28)
    - Bourgois, Christian/Press de la Cite/Ivan Nabokov, 1992-2001; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 29)
    - Byatt, Antonia, 1991; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 30)
    - Calendars, 1989-1998; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Cambridge: International Literature in English, 1992; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Carnegie Hall Commission: Honey and Rue, 1990-1993; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Chatto & Windus, 1986-1999; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - University of Chicago: "Global Fiction", Taught with Homi Bhabha, 1997-2000; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Clinton Global Initiative/President Clinton, 2006; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Professional Colleagues, 1992-2007; 2 folders (Box 168, Folder 7-8)
    - Condorcet Chair, 1994; 2 folders (Box 168, Folder 9-10)
    - Contracts, 1991-2003; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Cornell University, 1991-2007; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Cornell University Visiting Prof., 2000-2002; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Cornell University: A.D. White Professor-At-Large, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Curriculum Vitae, 2001-2005; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Dimock, Peter, 1996; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Fan Mail, 1997-2010; 2 boxes
      - Fan Mail, 2000-2010; 4 folders (Box 168, Folder 17-20)
      - Fan Mail: Weird Stuff, 1997-2010; 3 folders (Box 169, Folder 1-3)
      - Fan Mail: Answered by Form Letter, 2005-2009; 2 folders (Box 169, Folder 4-5)
    - Foreign Publishers, 1994-2002; 2 folders (Box 169, Folder 6-7)
    - Foreign Translators, 1985-2009; 2 folders (Box 169, Folder 8-9)
    - Forrest, Leon & Marianne, 1989-2000; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Foundations, 2002-2006; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 11)